gigacash.com 2006-06-16

# GigaCash™ - The Premiere Affiliate Marketing Engine

**Information about our Organisation and Web site**  
Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like [GigaCash.com](http://www.gigacash.com/). We are based in Los Angeles, California, USA, and our principal activities are Online Adult Entertainment and Affiliate Webmaster Resources. This privacy policy covers all subsidiary websites that exist in the GigaCash.com affiliate program, [listed here](http://www.gigacash.com/sites.php).

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**  
You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal or identifying data. 

**The services and links of our Web site**  
Our Web site enables you to openly communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data. Our Web site does not include links to third party Web service providers.

**Automatic Collection of Information**  
We automatically log personal data by means such as site programming or we link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for technical administration of the Web site and for enhanced customer administration. We use cookies to store personal data or we link information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for technical administration of the Web site and for enhanced customer administration.

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**  
We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We collect name, gender, geographic location, and e-mail address along with information concerning your employer or the organization you represent, your job title, and phone number. Additionally, personal and lifestyle details are also collected. Providing this information to us is strictly voluntary, and used for technical and customer administration of our Web site.  
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. We collect and use personal data for the additional purpose of distributing our opt-in newsletter and to send XBiz related announcement emails to registered Cosmic Village message board users, banner exchange users, and those that submit links.

Users can remove themselves by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all emails, or users can send their request to: [privacy2@gigacash.com](mailto:%70%72%69%76%61%63%79%32%40%67%69%67%61%63%61%73%68%2e%63%6f%6d)

We may collect and use personal data for the additional purpose of Age Verification. If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected 

**Children's Privacy**  
We do not knowingly collect personal data from children since use of our Web sites by children is prohibited. We do not provide any information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data.

Additionally, to ensure that children's privacy is respected on our Web site, we do not grant membership access to minors.

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**  
We do not disclose visitors' personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations. 

**Confidentiality / Security**  
We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data. We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction, or accidental loss.

All employees and others who have access to, or are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

**Access to the personal data we may hold about you**  
You can ask us, by sending an email to: [privacy2@gigacash.com](mailto:%70%72%69%76%61%63%79%32%40%67%69%67%61%63%61%73%68%2e%63%6f%6d) whether we are keeping personal data about you. Upon request, we will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, although we may first require proof of your identity. We provide this information without any charge.   
We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data erased, rectified, amended, or completed.

**Privacy Compliance**  
There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization.   
There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure.

**Privacy Support**  
If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact: [privacy2@gigacash.com](mailto:%70%72%69%76%61%63%79%32%40%67%69%67%61%63%61%73%68%2e%63%6f%6d)
